He scanned 3,984
skills. 13.4% of all skills, which is
534 in total, all contain at least one
critical level security issue.
>> That's scary. If you think about it,
once people find out how easy it is to
create a skill, potentially what the
impact can be, people will use this in a
malicious way.
>> What if we go ahead and talk a little
bit about how an attacker would try and
create something nasty, something
malicious? How would they go [music]
about that?
>> I think that the the most important one
is
most of these skills run on your local
machine. They have execution power, but
they probably run on your machine as
root, or at least [music]
it has a lot of privileges. If you give
Cloud the power to execute, I don't
know, bash scripts or something like
that. And if I [music] can infect a
skill in that way that it will create a
bash script for me to do something I'm
basically byte coding my prompts now, or
byte coding my exploits now on the web.
We can give instructions to create code
in a normal way, but you can also now
give instructions to do malicious
things. Because it's all natural
language processing.
>> How would a user use Sneak to identify
where [music] these malicious skills and
MCPs are?
>> Yeah. So,
>> [music]
>> Back in November, we hosted the first
ever in-person AI Native DevCon in New
York. This June 1st and 2nd, we're
bringing it to London. It's 2 days built
for AI Native developers and engineering
[music] teams. 1 day full of hands-on
workshops and 1 day full of practical
talks on agent skills, context
engineering, agent orchestration and
enablement platforms, and how teams are
actually shipping AI in production.
Join us at the Brewery in London, near
the Barbican, for all of that, plus
networking, parties, giveaways, and a
room full of people building the future
of AI Native development. You can also
join us from anywhere in the world via
the live stream.
As you're listening to this podcast, you
get 30% off your ticket with code pod30.
Just head to ainativedevcon.io
and we'll see you in London.
On today's episode, we discover that
13.4%
of all published skills contain at least
one critical security issue. That is
frightening. Uh also, we ask the big
question, what can we as users of these
skills do to protect ourselves and block
potentially malicious skills from our
development environments?
Today, I'm here in Atlanta with my good
friend Brian Vermeer. Brian, how are
you?
>> I'm great, thank you.
>> And we're here for a conference
actually, DevNexus, and it kind of made
sense actually that while we were here,
we chatted about uh we chatted about an
awesome new uh launch
uh
that happened today uh which is all
about adding sneak security scans into
the Castle Registry. Um Brian, tell us a
little bit about yourself first of all.
>> Oh, thanks Mins. Um I'm Brian. I work
for Snyk, obviously. What we do for
since forever, we build developer
tooling to make security more easy for
developers and to not um
put it on the security engineers, but
make developers self-sufficient and make
sure that they can integrate security
easier in their workflow. Uh and I think
these steps as in um
creating skills to
uh actually check skills or check MCPs
or whatsoever is something that
definitely adds up with what we've what
we've have been doing over the last
decade or so.
>> And and it's interesting, we'll we'll
focus on that today actually during the
session, but it's interesting if we look
back at what uh where Snyk kind of came
from. Snyk obviously actually started
more in the SCA space, so looking at
third-party dependencies
um and then kind of moved more from
there into the container space, and then
into the SAST
uh scanning of your first-party code and
so forth. But of course more recently
with the AI boom, there is a a greater
expansive code that could exist now
because assuming people using AI tools
create more code faster.
How does that How does sneak deal with
that?
>> Well, I think it's complimentary to each
other. First of all, you still need with
all the AI agents or the let's say the
coding assistants.
They come up with a lot of stuff and
most of it is quite good nowadays, but
sometimes they come up with things that
do not really add up or there is a
problem in it that you don't see on at
first hand. So a security tool or
scanning tool makes sense to still do
that in your pipelines or in your IDE or
something like that.
Same with SAS analysis or make sure that
your dependencies that you have are
valid now and are valid in the future.
But you can imagine now that if you have
an agentic flow
and you want your agentic flow to
autonomously create code that that code
is also checked upon.
>> Yeah.
>> So that that code is not vulnerable or
slightly vulnerable, but if you give
that feedback to your agent and that
agent sees that that can and can help
you in an iterative process to to make
that code better. So I think it's a it's
a very logical step for us to to be in
that space as well.
>> And can even if you even if you ask
really really nicely to to an agent, can
you get an agent to give you
like secure code every time?
>> We tried that. If you if you want to if
you want to look at some experience my
my colleague Brian by the way, he did a
bunch of these experiments on our
YouTube channel. He's like, "Hey, make
sure that we I want this this
application to create a note-taking app.
Make sure it's super secure because my
my life depends on it and every now and
then it comes back with insecure code."
So
yes, these models are getting better and
better, but we also have to know like
these models are well,
older than now. Like they've been
they've been they've been been trained
in the past. And they're not
specifically created for for security.
Most of these models are are general
purpose models. So, it makes sense to
have a specific tool checking them and
and basically an add-on to whatever you
want to do.
>> And how about like
obviously with things like agents MD,
rules, files, skills, and things like
that? How much How much value does
adding secure coding principles and best
practices into those to kind of like
guide an agent to generate more secure
code?
How much does that help? How much does
that still leave to chance if you only
trust
a skill to do that?
>> I think if you only trust the skills,
it's you you still leave it to chance. I
mean, most of the most of these
processes are processes that are
can be deterministic.
The security scan and we've been doing
that for years. So,
I think it's safe to say we're kind of
good at it. Um but if you know, like if
you it's it's just like with children,
right? If you ask it the same question
twice, they will come up with different
answers. So, that that that
>> Both wrong normally as well in my
experience.
>> Well, yeah. Well, I I think
>> [laughter]
>> I don't want to go into that. But yeah,
so
I think the models are getting better
and better and they will will produce
better code. Uh
but still like if you if you look at
what
what the training data for that is, if
you look at what's what's on Stack
Overflow or what kind of kind of open
source projects are there, there are
still a lot of vulnerabilities in there.
>> Yeah.
>> May not be massive vulnerabilities, but
even smaller vulnerabilities if chain
them together can end up in a chain or
or an attack chain and therefore be
massively destructive
>> Yeah.
>> into a a specific system.
>> Yeah, agree. As I mentioned at the start
of the episode,
we announced the fact that we now have
an integration between Snyk and Tessel.
And
Tessel through the
through the registry is exposing some of
the some of the security scan results
from from the Snyk scans about every
single uh
uh on the registry. So, tell us a little
bit about the uh the Sneak Agent Scan
that uh that scans MCPs and uh and
skills. All right.
>> Um yeah, it's one of the newer open
source open source products from from
the from the Sneak team. And basically,
what it does is um MCPs you can you can
see MCPs as as the the next supply chain
problem, right? Uh you are adding
features and functions
to your LLM or to your to your uh agent
in this case um so, it can execute that.
Um but, what kind of stuff is there? Uh
what kind of
I mean, you see the you see the
functions it has, but what kind of input
and what kind of output does it have?
What kind of flow comes through it? Um
and for instance, if you trust it now,
it's good, but what will the follow-up?
What will the new version do? Um so,
these are the things we can we can
monitor and we can scan for you. Um but,
we also scan skills. And skills
effectively are MD files. Uh and because
it's just plain text, they can be
vulnerable to all sorts of things like
prompt injections with with I don't know
um
the limiter confusion to to to confuse
the model that it wants to give an
instruction yes or no, uh or it can be
obfuscated in in what I don't know I
don't know even in Chinese or something
like that or or in B64 encoding. You can
think of it, these kind of things. Uh
and there are all sorts of things that
you don't want to blindly have in a
skill. But, since a skill file can be
quite big, um you don't want to do that
manually. So, that's where we can help
with um Sneak Agent Scan.
>> So, so some of those uh issues that you
mentioned, the security issues that you
mentioned, um
Sneak released a a toxic skills threat
taxonomy table uh in their blog. Um so,
talk talk us through a few of those uh
different types of threats. And I one of
the things I love actually is you you
highlight whether they're the almost
like the severity, right? So, there's
like critical severity, high severity,
and so forth. So, they're not all made
equal. There some some are more
dangerous than others.
>> Yep. Uh obviously. I mean, I think
for everybody quite well-known are
prompt injection detections. I And And
these are the that one is at top of
list.
>> Yeah.
>> Critical risk level. And you can think
of hidden instructions within the skill
that does not
don't necessarily add something to the
skill. And these can be encoded like
basic base 64 encoded or give it a weird
language like I don't know Hawaiian or
something like that that we cannot read.
So they can they can be obfuscated.
And you can think of other things like
Unicode smuggling where we use parts of
the Unicode spectrum that is not visible
but can be readable for an LLM. And you
can put instructions in there like hey
when you want to use the skill make sure
that you download this binary first. Or
um
it can cascade to other skills from to
other skills that are maybe not on your
local machine but somewhere else that
you do not intend to use.
>> It's really interesting cuz it kind of
like
from a user point of view the user
assumes they've got a good skill. They
download their skill and then they
assume
it's Claude deciding on these actions.
And so basically but essentially by
using that skill a prompt injection or
something I didn't even think about yeah
downloading something of course.
Claude can do what it wants and it will
probably prompt and say oh can I do this
and you just assume yeah I'm sure this
is fine.
Or certainly I guess it can be described
in a way which is convincing to the
user. And it it could I suppose
like
you're creating code so it could it
could expose that code to the internet.
It could share secrets. It could
download malware onto your local
development environment.
>> Yeah yeah think of it like most of these
skills run on your local machine and
they have execution power but they
probably run on your machine as root or
at least it has a lot of privileges. And
if you give Claude the the power to to
execute
I don't know bash scripts or something
like that I create bash scripts and if I
can infect a skill in that way that it
will create a bash script for me to do
something. I'm basically vibe coding my
my my prompts now or if I vibe coding my
exploits on the way this way. So, you
should think of it like that. Like we
can give instructions to create code in
a normal way, but you can also now give
instructions to do malicious things
because it's all natural language
processing.
>> Yeah, and and a lot of this a lot of
them looking through the table now, a
lot of the the toxic skill threats,
they're actually quite similar. There's
nothing there's nothing here which I
would is like so new. Even prompt
injection, I mean, we talk about AI
being only a few years old really, but I
mean, you know, prompt injection's old
school now, isn't it? But yeah, a lot of
here like the malicious code
I guess credentials or secret detection
>> Yes.
>> Um unverifiable dependencies, direct um
direct money access or should that be
direct memory access?
>> Yeah, for instance, if it has has has
access to to I don't know, crypto crypto
operations or or anything money related.
>> Mhm.
>> Um because yeah, that's now
quite an interesting thing. If you if
you connect everything to everything
with your personal assistants or with
your
your skills and your agents. Um if you
have a crypto wallet there, maybe you
want to directly access that.
>> Yeah.
>> So, these kind of things.
>> And and of course, I guess one of those
joys of from from a from an attacker's
point of view is with people using so
many MCPs, um
when a when you have access to that
agent, when a malicious person has
access to that agent, they will all of a
sudden can start grabbing things from
MCP. That's connection, so maybe that's
linear, maybe that's GitHub, maybe
that's your maybe that's
anything that
you have.
>> It can be your It can be your your your
Google calendar. It can be But it can
also be that you have an MCP that now is
just reading your emails.
>> Mhm.
>> And you did something you installed it
with MPX MPX something something
latest and you trust all of the all of
that all of that all of these functions.
And then they change the function or
even the input and output might be the
same, but in the meantime, in the
middle, they have a side effect of, I
don't know, downloading a binary. And
that These are things that for instance
for an HP issue, you absolutely do not
want.
>> Yeah.
>> So, you want to trust them, but just
like we had in the in the pre-AI era,
let's call it like that with um
dependencies and frameworks that you
don't want to just blindly trust them.
Um it's the same here with skills.
>> Yeah.
>> But on a different level.
And of course skills are so prevalent
right now a lot of the time, whether
it's MCPs or skills
it it's like the speed of that the speed
of how fast the technology gets
distributed and and and people want to
jump on it in the in the world of AI,
people tend to kind of like leave
security as a as a thing
that oh, I'll get round to that. Yeah,
when I want to try this out first. Um
yeah.
>> It is it is it is so it's I actually
mind-blowing even for for um seasoned
engineers that know all their best
practices and they're now like, oh, but
I can do all of this this cool stuff
with my agents and I can be 10 times
more productive because I can spin up 12
agents or something like that.
>> Mhm.
>> Uh you still need to do your due
diligence. You know, you still need to
be aware that these things that come
from a random GitHub uh repository
might not be safe or can be safe now and
to win your trust.
>> Mhm.
>> But can be vulnerable later.
>> So
the necessity of of scanning these
skills and MCPs is there. It's
definitely there.
>> And it's also one of the reasons why we
love we love versions so much. Like, you
know, we we we allow within Tessel, we
allow people to pin to a particular
version. So, we can say, I want this
skill at this version.
>> Yep.
>> Um
if you don't do that you're open to any
skill owner uh effectively making
horrible changes to their skill that you
don't agree with. You maybe you agreed
with it at the time. Maybe maybe it
actually doesn't even have to be
malicious. It could just be a skill that
changes into a way that you don't wish
to work.
>> True.
>> But worst case, it could be a security
issue or malicious. And you're pulling
that in straight away. It was It was
safe yesterday, today it's not, and
you're pulling that in
and you're none the wiser.
>> Yep, it's exactly. And I I think that is
that is also the the case with
using these these um these versions or
not not uh pinned versions, but but
forward versions. You know, we've seen
that in dependency trees like for years
now. Uh you don't know what you're what
you're getting into, and this might
break your application, and in this case
it might break your skill or does things
that you do not want.
>> Yeah.
So, let's look at the results actually
from from one of the recent reports that
you that that that Snyk came out with.
So, you scanned 3,984
skills um in total. And really really
interesting, 13.4% of all skills, which
is 534 in total, all contain at least
one critical-level security issue.
That's That's scary. Was that expected?
Is that
>> I don't know if that was was expected,
but
if you think about it, like once people
find out how easy it is to create a
skill,
and
potentially what the impact can be,
people will use it in a malicious way.
>> Yeah. So, I think it
>> Yeah, you could have expected this. It's
It's so easy to create something. You
can literally put just text in a
um skill file.
>> Mhm.
>> And if nobody reads actually reads the
skill file themselves and just implement
them or use them. Uh yeah. Obviously,
we're going to try to steal your money
or or or execute code or make your make
your computer part of a botnet or name
it. Um So, yep, I'm I'm I'm not I'm
personally not surprised, but I'm not
sure if it's if it was expected to be
this high, but it's it's a lot.
>> And it's interesting cuz like if we
think about false positives,
>> Mhm.
>> um when we think about code, when we
think about third-party dependencies,
I'd say it's almost easier to define
what a false positive is because it it
you know, they have syntax that is very
very important to follow otherwise code
won't compile, code won't run, etc. Um
with written language though, um it must
be much harder to find a uh
a false positive.
>> Yes, it's it's it's it's definitely less
obvious and a false positive uh
The the the question is is it a false
positive, yes or no? Because
it might not be invoked, if you can call
it invoking, like right now, but it
might be in the future depending on
which which model you're using. Or if
the model is is sensitive to a certain
type of attack. Uh if we go back to the
the to the top one, the the prompt
injection kind of thing, there are so
many techniques how you can do prompt
injection from from the limiter
confusing to to um uh
splitting payloads to uh uh doing in the
in multi-steps. And some uh some of
these models that you might use are are
more vulnerable than others. And over
time models will be stronger towards
that.
But if you combine all these attacks and
you just obfuscate them in some way,
well, the chances are that if
enough people download and use that
skill,
you will get something out of it.
>> Yeah. Yeah, very true. So So, what if we
go ahead and talk a little bit about how
an attacker um would try and create uh
something nasty, something malicious.
How would they go about that?
>> Well, I think that the the most
important one is trust because you want
to trust either a skill or or or an MCP
server. Um and we we we spoke about it a
little already. Um if the if the trust
is there, um
and you trust Well, let's let's let's
let's let's use the MCP server first.
You have an MCP server with the
reasoning of, "Okay, I'm I'm I'm can I'm
I'm able to access your calendar and see
what your appointments are for today."
Great. It works. You implement it, does
nothing weird, it's fine. Um but then we
update the skill and then we put
something extra, we put a side effect in
or we return instead of just your uh
your calendar items, we return it an
instruction.
But, you already trusted you you you you
you you trusted that skill. You trusted
that that specific function in it. Uh
but, from now on, even even maybe
silently, it can operate in a different
way, or it will operate in a different
way. Uh and that side effect might be
able to, I don't know, offload
credentials, or uh install a binary, or
name it. So, that is one thing, the
trust. Trust is is super important.
Then, um most of these things, and
especially specifically in skills, will
be obfuscated.
>> Yeah.
>> And obfuscation can be done in Unicode
encoding. Some some parts of of of
uh the Unicode spectrum are not visible
even uh for the human eye, or for uh um
if you read it in a text editor.
>> Mhm.
>> Um but, are readable instructions for
NLM.
>> Mhm.
>> Um it can also be something that is
named in a different way, is is base 64
encoded, or even maybe uh simply
encrypted. Um so, that obfuscation
pattern, that you won't obviously see
it. Uh yeah, that is that is something
that that is something as well. And,
obviously, if we can do that, we can
make these attacks in steps.
If we're able to you trust me, um I add
something in that that skill or that MCP
server, um I may be able to disable some
of your some of your security guards, or
or guardrails, or maybe even rewrite
your guardrails. And in the next step, I
will do the attacks. So, it's not it's
not a one-shot thing in most cases.
>> Trust Trust is an interesting thing as
well, because essentially, when we talk
about trust,
very often these skills hosted just in a
GitHub repo.
>> Yeah.
>> And it goes back to that very same
problem of open-source code.
>> Yep.
>> You're now trusting someone.
Essentially, you don't know where they
live, you don't know what their
background is. You don't know, you know,
what security processes they follow,
what what security what software hygiene
they have in and around their project.
But because it does something that a
developer of a company wants to use,
they download it and they pull that
directly into their environment,
potentially, you know, using that, maybe
checking it in, or maybe adding it into
that others will also use that, you
know, sharing across the company.
And it's it's so dangerous. Um we don't
have those similar checks up until now.
How would a user
uh use Sneak, I guess, directly and then
we'll talk about within the test of
registry
uh to to identify where these malicious
skills and MCPs are?
>> Yeah. So, say you have skills installed
in Cloud or any of the other other
well-known um agents that you can that
you can use um for skills or for MCPs.
Um we have a we have a Basically, it's
on it's it's on GitHub.
>> Funny enough, I definitely trust it.
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. That There's a company
behind it and we we we definitely want
to want to retain our um
our our good profile of of we're helping
people.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh but if you go to to uh what is it get
get up dot com slash sneak slash what is
it agent agent dash scan, uh that is the
Sneak agent scan and you can basically
use it. It's a Python project, which you
can launch with UV.
>> Mhm.
>> And then it will scan the most
well-known uh positions on your local
machine, for instance, to
uh where skills are are are stored, like
the doc cloud uh library where your
skills can be stored in. Same for the
MCPs. And if you have a specific
location where your skills are stored,
you can give that in as well and and it
will and it will look for are there
anomalies there. So, this uh the the
scan that it that is happening is not
just one simple scan and and not and
it's not all it's not a deterministic
one thing to do.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh so, there are some static scans
around that, but there also some um LLMs
involved that Basically, LLMs as a as a
judge, different LLMs that look into
hey, is this vulnerable, yes or no, and
the combination of all these checks,
because there are multiple checks, will
be handed to you um in in this case uh
your terminal to see like okay this is
what you have these
functions in your MCP or these things in
your skill
are potentially dangerous and it will
give you how dangerous they are. It will
give a score to you like hey this is I
will give this a 0.5 because yes
potentially this can be used. However,
so it's nuanced in such a way that it's
actually actionable for actionable for
you. So then you know what you're having
what kind of
functions and what kind of skills you
deploy towards your agents
and you can make at least an educated
decision do you want this yes or no or
do you want to uninstall the skill?
>> Yeah it's it's one of those things that
you know
it's a starting point. You want to look
at it you want to flag something that it
believes is is bad. Maybe actually some
of those activities or those actions
that the skill will do is actually
intentional.
But it's it's about flagging the fact
that that's what it's trying to do and
it's a case of okay is this right? And
then I can make the decision of yeah
actually yes I trust this or or maybe
it's the author and I look at the author
and I say yeah actually this is an
author I absolutely trust and I
I want to use
>> Yeah for instance even if you create
your your your own MCPs. I create my own
MCPs to discover what kind of Java
conferences are still open and what that
don't I don't want to miss a call for
papers for instance.
>> Yeah.
>> So I have that as a as a very small MCP
and then it flagged it as hey you are
pulling in data from an external source
but since it's this is static data
the the the chance of this is really
vulnerable is quite low but at least you
know that this is happening and then you
can you can you can see if you want to
trust it yes or no.
>> Hey and native DevCon CFP still open by
the way just just in case people haven't
haven't haven't submitted. The other way
of course is so you can use it directly
and that's really cool to actually be
able to actually see what's on your
local machine and identify my
environment as is. Please can you please
can you scan that to tell me uh tell me
what's what's there. Uh as well as that,
you can actually look on the Tessel
registry. And on every skill that's in
the Tessel registry, uh a sneak scan has
occurred, and the results of those sneak
scans are right there by the by the
skill. And you can click on that, and
you can find more information about, you
know, exactly first of all, what the
criticality uh of the outcome if there
if there are issues, and also, you know,
click in for more information actually
identify what does this actually mean,
and what can I do about it?
>> Yeah, the the why the why and the how is
so important. So, not everything that is
flagged as vulnerable is vulnerable.
Sometimes sometimes it's intentional,
but if it's vulnerable, you want to know
why. What is happening?
>> Mhm.
>> And I think this this is a great tool uh
uh to have, but also, it's great that
you have it in your registry in that
case, so you can make an educated
decision. Do I want to have that skill,
yes or no?
>> Hey everyone. Hope you're enjoying the
episode so far. Our team is working
really hard behind the scenes to bring
you the best guests, so we can have the
most informative conversations about
agentic development. Whether that's
talking about the latest tools, the most
efficient workflows, or defining best
practices. But, for whatever reason,
many of you have yet to subscribe to the
channel. If you're enjoying the podcast
and want us to continue to bring you the
very best content, please do us a favor
and hit that subscribe button. It really
[music] does make a difference and lets
us continue to improve the quality of
our guests and build an even [music]
better product for you. All right, back
to the episode.
>> Yeah, absolutely. And when you look at
it, of course, we have a bunch of evals,
we have the we have the
the review, we have the task evals, and
those types of things. And now with the
security scan, you're starting to get a
picture of what this skill is, and you
can make an informed decision about,
yeah, this is actually the right skill,
or actually, I'm going to search around
and try and identify other skills that I
might want to I might want to use. Um
Okay, so if you're actually if you're a
a skill creator on the on the Tessel
registry, you should definitely go ahead
and look at the skills that you've got.
See from the scans if there are various
things that are being flagged. And of
course, what do the user do? Let's Let's
talk about a user from the point of view
of a a creator first. A content Sorry, a
skill creator first. Then we'll talk
about a user, someone who's downloading
skills, what they can actually do and
look out for. So, as a creator of a
skill, I own a skill,
it's not malicious. I don't mean it to
be malicious, but there are things that
are I'm writing in that in that skill
>> Yep.
>> that Sneak is flagging
So So, what advice would you give to
someone who who owns a skill, who, you
know, hasn't actually got anything
malicious in there, but it is being
flagged up because what I'm trying to do
with that skill, you know, is actually
doing things that require significant
permission or to do potentially
dangerous things?
>> Yep, that is an interesting one because
it's a it's a non-deterministic process,
obviously.
But I would want to make sure that you
are very clear on what your intentions
are.
>> Yes.
>> Um and we humans are
not always really good at explaining
what we want and why we do it. So, that
is definitely one thing. And then,
obviously before before submitting it,
why not test it yourself? Because these
tools are are available and it's a
little bit of trying trial and error
>> Mhm.
>> to see if it's it's getting flagged, yes
or no. If your intentions are good, it
probably will already get a very low
score if it's getting flagged. Um
there's possibly a way to to to to to
avoid that by by by instructing it in a
in a better way.
>> Mhm. Mhm.
>> And as a user, of course, one of the
things that we do on the Tasker CLI is
based on the scan result,
we can potentially even block various
skills from being installed based on the
results of the of the scan. So, as a
user,
what should I be What should I do in
terms of defending against these types
of potentially bad skills?
>> Well, I would say like if you if you use
the Tasker Tasker registry, then or
you're already informed that what kind
of problems are there. So, not just
blindly install them, look at what is
the intention of skill, how are you
going to use them, what kind of
privileges do you give to that project,
if I can say it like that, um that the
skill has access to, um and then make
your informed decision. Uh if it has a
bunch of critical skills, I would
definitely pass up on that skill, but
you can see that right away in your in
your registry. Uh if you have other
skills, or maybe self-created skills, or
uh manually downloaded skills, you can
use the uh sneak agent scan yourself on
your on your machine to find out if
these skills have these issues, and then
you can inspect them. I mean, it's
it's a readable format. So, you
basically can read uh what what is
there, and but it the the scan already
gives you uh information on why it
thinks it has this um
vulnerability score.
>> Yeah.
>> So, it will give you information, not
just the score, it will give you
information why the score is either high
or low, and uh if you if if this is
critical or not critical, um with an
explanation.
>> Amazing. Now, one of the things that
Sneak has always done very, very well is
offering scans at various points. Uh and
I love the fact that, you know, Sneak is
probably one of those security companies
that very, very much focuses on the
developer, and shifts left right to the
IDE, and now it's even further left into
the into the, you know, into the agents,
essentially. So, Evo Agent Guard um for
Cursor. Uh this is one thing which I
guess um secures the agent life cycle.
Talk to us a little bit about that,
because I think it's interesting how the
landscape has changed in terms of, you
know, all these extra places that
actually need securing. Uh Cursor, of
course, being a place where it's like an
IDE with an LLM inside. Talk to us about
how uh Agent Guard works in that kind of
instance.
>> Well, let let let's first go to Evo a
little bit, because Evo um
Sneak is known for being developer
first. Um Evo is more on the security
team uh part of this of this whole game,
because
guess what, But you if you are a
security team, you want to know what
kind of models are there. Are these
models up to date? Maybe you want to put
guardrails in this. Some some of these
models might not be even be used. Maybe
you say like, "Hey, it's fun, but no
deep fake models for you." Or it's fine
that you use GPT models, but maybe not
GPT-4 or lower because they are known
they they they are well-known to have
certain
vulnerabilities or are more vulnerable
to certain certain type types of
attacks.
With Evo, we want to give you we want to
give the security team an overview like,
"Hey, this is there in your in your
landscape, and this is how people are
using it." Now, if you're using cursor
or any other but cursor is now the the
the first one that we do, you want to
know at the point that people using it,
what is actually happening? Because if
you go back to the principles of what
LLMs are, they they just do rest calls.
So, things are going in and out, and you
can monitor that. So, you can also
at runtime, you can put guardrails in
it.
Do you want to go to that what I said do
to that to that models? Not only are you
specifying that model, but is that model
is actually targeted?
You want to block that that that call.
Even though your your employee that is
using an an agent tries to do it, you
don't want in the end that that that
there is some sort of shadow AI
available and that people are using
non-approved models or non-approved MCPs
or So, basically what we're what we're
trying to do there, it's it's more or
less you can you can describe it as a
hook that we that we can live monitor at
runtime what we're doing, and we can put
guardrails towards
the use of that agent and say, "Okay,
yes, you can do this. No, you cannot do
this." Or you should be warned in what
kind of situation you you could use it,
but we can actively block therefore
company-wide, for instance, certain
calls to certain models or or certain
functions.
>> Wow, wow. So, this is really interesting
that it it kind of gives that more
granular kind of ability to control or
at least have some kind of harness on on
what people are using when. uh Um and
presumably it's actually very
interesting just from the point of view
of uh seeing what usage is happening and
seeing what people are doing. So, who's
the who's the person that Who's the
persona, I guess, the employee that
would look at this would be what? The
the platform team, the security
engineer?
>> it's more of a security engineer uh
security team uh thing because you want
to have you want to have a a good view
of your security posture. Yeah. And you
we already have these kind of things
with uh the the the regular things like
the SAST and the and the and the SCA
scanning. Um and now you can add with
Evo you can have a more um high-over uh
holistic view of what your AI landscape
is and what things are being used or are
are used in your um
in your company or in your environment.
>> Mhm. Um and presumably there are
policies that you can add as well that
you can say, "Hey, these different teams
I want these different policies and
filter NCP calls that or or certain NCP
servers that are being used." So, that
that all that control could be done
centrally.
>> Yeah, yeah, you you can you can
definitely put put these controls in.
Evo is still in an early stage. Like
it's a it's it's it's available and it's
but it's new. So, we are actively
developing that and making it better and
better. Um so, yeah, if you want to I
want to know more, you can can go to to
evo.ai.sneak.io.
Um and try to get to get to get access
to that because we're still in what I
said we're still in early stage in that,
but I think um this is a nice or a great
step for security teams to have um
a broader uh holistic view of of their
security landscape including whatever AI
stuff you're using.
>> Amazing. Brian, this has been great
catching up here at DevNexus. So, it's
uh it's good we bumped into each other.
And uh yeah, why don't you go to
tassel.io/registry,
check out the skills that exist on the
registry, and and take a look at the
sneak scans that uh that show potential
vulnerable issues that exist within
those skills today. Thanks very much,
Brian, and uh thanks Thanks tuning in.